Hey, do me a favor
and take table seven.
(Bernadette:)You mean the one
with my 118-pound
rock-hard stud of a fiancé
(Bernadette:)who's prone to canker
sores and pinkeye?
(Penny:)Nah, I prefer to look at it as
the one with my ex-boyfriend
(Penny:)and his gorgeous, successful
and sophisticated girlfriend,
(Penny:)who makes me feel like
a toothless Okie.
(Bernadette:)Do you want me to spill
hot soup on her?
(Penny:)Oh, please-- you're not
that kind of person.
(Bernadette:)I know.
(Bernadette:)But if she orders
something low-fat
(Bernadette:)I'll totally give her
the full-fat version.
(Leonard:)Uh, that's my water.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Leonard:)My water.
You're drinking it.
D-Dear Lord!
(Sheldon:)Have you been drinking it?
(Leonard:)Yes. It's my water.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's it then.
(Sheldon:)I'm dead.
(Leonard:)Here we go...
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, do I really need
to connect the dots for you?
(Sheldon:)The backwash into this glass
(Sheldon:)is every pathogen that calls
your mouth home, sweet home.
(Sheldon:)Not to mention the visitors who
arrive on the dancing tongue